<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>admin &#8211; Banda Ultra Larga</title>
	<atom:link href="/author/admin/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 20:44:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/cropped-2024-01-28-02_24_48-logo-cie@2x-1.png-800×440-Copy-1-32x32.png</url>
	<title>admin &#8211; Banda Ultra Larga</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>GM Quader&#8217;s opponents in an attempt to bring down Roshan, meeting on Sunday</title>
		<link>/gm-quaders-opponents-in-an-attempt-to-bring-down-roshan-meeting-on-sunday/</link>
					<comments>/gm-quaders-opponents-in-an-attempt-to-bring-down-roshan-meeting-on-sunday/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 20:44:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10905</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[However, Japa General Secretary Mujibul Haque Chunnu is not willing to give importance to this activity of the opposition. He said, those who have resigned, they are welcome if they form a new party. This bodes well for democracy. But if the sponsor is Roshan Ershad, it remains to be seen. There was tension in ... <a title="GM Quader&#8217;s opponents in an attempt to bring down Roshan, meeting on Sunday" class="read-more" href="/gm-quaders-opponents-in-an-attempt-to-bring-down-roshan-meeting-on-sunday/" aria-label="More on GM Quader&#8217;s opponents in an attempt to bring down Roshan, meeting on Sunday">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>However, Japa General Secretary Mujibul Haque Chunnu is not willing to give importance to this activity of the opposition. He said, those who have resigned, they are welcome if they form a new party. This bodes well for democracy. But if the sponsor is Roshan Ershad, it remains to be seen.</p>
<p>There was tension in Japan even before the election. It has increased after the January 7 election landslide. Several senior leaders including Co-Chairman Kazi Feroze Rasheed have lost their posts after criticizing the leadership of Japa Chairman GM Quader for taking part in the election only after getting concession of seats from Awami League for his wife Sherifa Quader.</p>
<p>Several candidates of the party withdrew from the election before the polls. Their complaint was that GM Quader received money from the government for participating in the elections. He did not take notice of the candidates put to the vote. Opposition has gained a new dimension with the news that Sherifa Kader, who lost his bail in the last election, will go to the 12th Parliament in the reserved seat. In a press conference led by the ousted presidium member Shafiqul Islam, Japa announced the resignation of about 700 leaders at the metropolitan, police station and ward levels.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/gm-quaders-opponents-in-an-attempt-to-bring-down-roshan-meeting-on-sunday/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bangladeshi crew is on the ship damaged by the Houthi attack</title>
		<link>/the-bangladeshi-crew-is-on-the-ship-damaged-by-the-houthi-attack/</link>
					<comments>/the-bangladeshi-crew-is-on-the-ship-damaged-by-the-houthi-attack/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 20:44:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10903</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Yemen&#8217;s Houthi rebels have attacked a British oil tanker in the Gulf of Aden. After Friday&#8217;s attack, the Marlin Luanda caught fire on its starboard side. The fire on the ship is still burning on Saturday. News from NDTV Quoting the Indian Navy, the media report said that the ship damaged by the Houthi attack ... <a title="The Bangladeshi crew is on the ship damaged by the Houthi attack" class="read-more" href="/the-bangladeshi-crew-is-on-the-ship-damaged-by-the-houthi-attack/" aria-label="More on The Bangladeshi crew is on the ship damaged by the Houthi attack">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Yemen&#8217;s Houthi rebels have attacked a British oil tanker in the Gulf of Aden. After Friday&#8217;s attack, the Marlin Luanda caught fire on its starboard side. The fire on the ship is still burning on Saturday. News from NDTV</p>
<p>Quoting the Indian Navy, the media report said that the ship damaged by the Houthi attack had 22 Indians and a Bangladeshi crew on board. Their guided missile destroyer INS Visakhapatnam quickly responded after receiving a plea for help from the ship. Now this warship is trying to control the oil tanker fire.</p>
<p>In a statement, the Indian Navy said its forces are always committed to maintaining smooth sailing at sea.</p>
<p>The giant ship Marlin Luanda was attacked shortly after arriving in the Gulf of Aden. The Houthi rebels attacked the ship with anti-ship missiles.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/the-bangladeshi-crew-is-on-the-ship-damaged-by-the-houthi-attack/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jubo League procession in Ramda: Initiative not blocked, no case filed</title>
		<link>/jubo-league-procession-in-ramda-initiative-not-blocked-no-case-filed/</link>
					<comments>/jubo-league-procession-in-ramda-initiative-not-blocked-no-case-filed/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 20:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10901</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It is known that the procession was led by Johnny Hasan Labu, President of Municipal Jubo League, at Singra Bus Stand area at 11:30 am on Friday. In the viral video, it can be seen that most of the people who took part in the procession were carrying different types of indigenous weapons. Some of ... <a title="Jubo League procession in Ramda: Initiative not blocked, no case filed" class="read-more" href="/jubo-league-procession-in-ramda-initiative-not-blocked-no-case-filed/" aria-label="More on Jubo League procession in Ramda: Initiative not blocked, no case filed">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It is known that the procession was led by Johnny Hasan Labu, President of Municipal Jubo League, at Singra Bus Stand area at 11:30 am on Friday. In the viral video, it can be seen that most of the people who took part in the procession were carrying different types of indigenous weapons. Some of them had ramadas, some iron rods, Chinese axes and hansua. Half a hundred activists took part in the march led by Labu wearing a helmet. Among them, Bayjid Hossain, president of Ward No. 9 of Municipal Jubo League, Anwar Hossain Saudagar, former Publicity and Publication Secretary of Municipal Volunteer League, Barat Ali Saudagar and Jahangir Saudagar, Jubo League workers, were seen holding weapons. The office of the CNG-powered Auto-Rickshaw Owners Association was vandalized while chanting slogans. Panic spread in the area when people openly marched with arms on the Natore-Bogra highway.</p>
<p>Singra Municipal Jubo League President Johnny Hasan Labu said that the administration could not stop extortion in public transport for 15 years. Therefore, this march has been done with the traders with weapons to stop the levy.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Ranju Mondal, general secretary of the CNG-driven auto-rickshaw owners association, did not give any answer when asked about the reason for not filing a case in the case of office vandalism. However, he said, the incident happened due to a misunderstanding. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/jubo-league-procession-in-ramda-initiative-not-blocked-no-case-filed/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pressure is mounting on Israel</title>
		<link>/pressure-is-mounting-on-israel/</link>
					<comments>/pressure-is-mounting-on-israel/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 20:43:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10899</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[UN Secretary-General Antonio Guterres said he expected Israel to &#8216;duly comply&#8217; with ICZ orders. However, the day after the order, Israel increased the bombing of Gaza on Saturday. Another 174 Palestinians were killed in one day. 310 people were injured. Civilians are being shot like birds. CNN&#8217;s release of such a video has caused an ... <a title="Pressure is mounting on Israel" class="read-more" href="/pressure-is-mounting-on-israel/" aria-label="More on Pressure is mounting on Israel">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>UN Secretary-General Antonio Guterres said he expected Israel to &#8216;duly comply&#8217; with ICZ orders. However, the day after the order, Israel increased the bombing of Gaza on Saturday. Another 174 Palestinians were killed in one day. 310 people were injured. Civilians are being shot like birds. CNN&#8217;s release of such a video has caused an uproar.</p>
<p>The ICJ ordered that Israel must take all measures to prevent genocide in Gaza and ensure the provision of &#8216;essential basic services&#8217;, but said nothing about a ceasefire. </p>
<p>After the order, South African President Cyril Ramaphosa, who prosecuted the genocide, said, &#8216;Israel faces trial before the international community. Today, their crimes against the Palestinians have been exposed.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/pressure-is-mounting-on-israel/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arakan Army is becoming a factor in Rohingya repatriation</title>
		<link>/arakan-army-is-becoming-a-factor-in-rohingya-repatriation/</link>
					<comments>/arakan-army-is-becoming-a-factor-in-rohingya-repatriation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 20:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10897</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The situation in Myanmar is becoming increasingly complicated. This has a direct impact on Rohingya repatriation. In 2021, the government before the army seized power was persuaded by Bangladesh to repatriate. Later, after the junta took power, communication was stopped for a long time. However, after some visible steps in the repatriation of Rohingyas, the ... <a title="Arakan Army is becoming a factor in Rohingya repatriation" class="read-more" href="/arakan-army-is-becoming-a-factor-in-rohingya-repatriation/" aria-label="More on Arakan Army is becoming a factor in Rohingya repatriation">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The situation in Myanmar is becoming increasingly complicated. This has a direct impact on Rohingya repatriation. In 2021, the government before the army seized power was persuaded by Bangladesh to repatriate. Later, after the junta took power, communication was stopped for a long time. However, after some visible steps in the repatriation of Rohingyas, the civil war situation in Arakan took a new complicated shape. Experts say that in the current situation there, Bangladesh will have to keep in touch with the armed rebel group Arakan Army to repatriate the Rohingya in the coming days.</p>
<p>The situation in Myanmar is changing rapidly. The rebel groups are occupying one area after another. The junta is losing control in many places. This has added a new dimension to the Rohingya crisis.</p>
<p>The Arakan Army has recently captured an important area near the Bangladesh-India border.<br />
However, diplomatic sources in Dhaka and Naypyidaw say that the junta is not at all upset about what the Arakan Army has done or how much land it has occupied. Because, even if the whole of Rakhine is occupied, the Arakan Army will fear losing that area again until the junta admits that it has lost or lost the territory. And if the junta wants to, it can immediately recover the lost areas by naval, air and army.</p>
<p>But the question arises, why the junta is losing these areas. A diplomat told Samakal on condition of anonymity that the areas occupied by the Arakan Army are almost all jungle and inaccessible. Myanmar is not willing to spend more resources and troops in these areas. Many of the army are leaving the service as they have been in the war for a long time.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/arakan-army-is-becoming-a-factor-in-rohingya-repatriation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Agriculture Minister&#8217;s 50-day action plan to bring fallow land under cultivation</title>
		<link>/agriculture-ministers-50-day-action-plan-to-bring-fallow-land-under-cultivation/</link>
					<comments>/agriculture-ministers-50-day-action-plan-to-bring-fallow-land-under-cultivation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 20:42:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10895</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[After receiving the responsibility as the Minister of Agriculture, the Minister of Agriculture informed about the plan of meeting with farmers across the country to increase the production of crops. Md. Abdus Shaheed. As part of this, he held the first courtyard meeting. About five hundred farmers were present in the meeting held in the ... <a title="Agriculture Minister&#8217;s 50-day action plan to bring fallow land under cultivation" class="read-more" href="/agriculture-ministers-50-day-action-plan-to-bring-fallow-land-under-cultivation/" aria-label="More on Agriculture Minister&#8217;s 50-day action plan to bring fallow land under cultivation">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After receiving the responsibility as the Minister of Agriculture, the Minister of Agriculture informed about the plan of meeting with farmers across the country to increase the production of crops. Md. Abdus Shaheed. As part of this, he held the first courtyard meeting.</p>
<p>About five hundred farmers were present in the meeting held in the courtyard of farmer Indu Bhushan Pal Niru of Noagaon village of Srimangal upazila on Saturday morning. Agriculture Minister asked the farmers why the land of Aman paddy harvesting village is still fallow.</p>
<p>The minister directed the local agriculture department to formulate an action plan within the next 50 days on how to bring cultivable fallow land under cultivation in Moulvibazar district, what crops can be grown on which land. He said, there is a lot of cultivable land. Now is the Boro season, but all the land here is lying fallow after harvesting the Aman paddy. We have to find ways to utilize these lands.</p>
<p>At this time, the minister ordered BADC to take action plan to solve the irrigation problem. He said that more agricultural machinery will be given at subsidized prices to solve the labor crisis.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/agriculture-ministers-50-day-action-plan-to-bring-fallow-land-under-cultivation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This time there is a demand to have a temple in place of Gnanabapi Masjid</title>
		<link>/this-time-there-is-a-demand-to-have-a-temple-in-place-of-gnanabapi-masjid/</link>
					<comments>/this-time-there-is-a-demand-to-have-a-temple-in-place-of-gnanabapi-masjid/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 20:42:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10893</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[After Babri Masjid, there was a Hindu temple at the site of Gnanabapi Masjid in Varanasi, Uttar Pradesh, India, according to the Archeology Department of the country. The Archaeological Survey of India (ASI) has conducted a survey on this. As a result of the survey, it is claimed that there was a temple there before ... <a title="This time there is a demand to have a temple in place of Gnanabapi Masjid" class="read-more" href="/this-time-there-is-a-demand-to-have-a-temple-in-place-of-gnanabapi-masjid/" aria-label="More on This time there is a demand to have a temple in place of Gnanabapi Masjid">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After Babri Masjid, there was a Hindu temple at the site of Gnanabapi Masjid in Varanasi, Uttar Pradesh, India, according to the Archeology Department of the country. The Archaeological Survey of India (ASI) has conducted a survey on this. As a result of the survey, it is claimed that there was a temple there before the construction of the mosque. The mosque was built in 1669 by Mughal Emperor Aurangzeb. BBC news</p>
<p>In the middle of last year, the Varanasi District Court ordered the ASI to conduct a survey of the mosque premises. Based on four months of survey, scientific observations, study of architectural features, patterns, inscriptions, art and sculptures, it is easy to say that a Hindu temple existed there before the construction of the present structure, the published survey report said.</p>
<p>Anupam Dwivedi, lawyer for plaintiff Rakhi Singh in the case, termed the survey as very important. He said, &#8216;This report will strengthen our case. It is very important for the cases in terms of evidence.&#8217;</p>
<p>However, Muslims have informed that they received a copy of the ASI report last Thursday night. SM Yasin, joint secretary of Anjuman Intezamiya Mosque, who is in charge of managing the Gnanabapi Masjid, said, &#8220;This is a report, not a judgment.&#8221; The report is of 839 pages. It will take time to survey and analyze. Lawyers and experts will be consulted. Then it will be taken to the court for consideration.&#8217;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/this-time-there-is-a-demand-to-have-a-temple-in-place-of-gnanabapi-masjid/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Agreeing to Sweden&#8217;s NATO membership, Türkiye is getting US F-16 fighter jets</title>
		<link>/agreeing-to-swedens-nato-membership-turkiye-is-getting-us-f-16-fighter-jets/</link>
					<comments>/agreeing-to-swedens-nato-membership-turkiye-is-getting-us-f-16-fighter-jets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 20:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10891</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The US State Department informed the US Congress on Friday night of the formal approval of the fighter jets. The ministry told Congress that an agreement to sell fighter jets to Greece as well as Turkey has been approved. Under the agreement, the United States will provide 40 F-35 fighter jets to Greece for $8.6 ... <a title="Agreeing to Sweden&#8217;s NATO membership, Türkiye is getting US F-16 fighter jets" class="read-more" href="/agreeing-to-swedens-nato-membership-turkiye-is-getting-us-f-16-fighter-jets/" aria-label="More on Agreeing to Sweden&#8217;s NATO membership, Türkiye is getting US F-16 fighter jets">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The US State Department informed the US Congress on Friday night of the formal approval of the fighter jets. The ministry told Congress that an agreement to sell fighter jets to Greece as well as Turkey has been approved. Under the agreement, the United States will provide 40 F-35 fighter jets to Greece for $8.6 billion. </p>
<p>In 2021, Turkey applied to the United States to buy the first advanced fighter jet. However, Turkey&#8217;s refusal to accept Sweden&#8217;s NATO membership has left tensions in the alliance. As a result, the US did not approve the sale of warplanes to Ankara. Turkey objects, Sweden supports and harbors Kurdish separatists. Türkiye has identified the Kurds as a terrorist group.</p>
<p>However, after more than a year, Turkish parliamentarians approved Sweden&#8217;s application on January 23. After only four days, the United States approved the sale of the warplane. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/agreeing-to-swedens-nato-membership-turkiye-is-getting-us-f-16-fighter-jets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shamim Osman is upset because DC-SP did not come to the rally</title>
		<link>/shamim-osman-is-upset-because-dc-sp-did-not-come-to-the-rally/</link>
					<comments>/shamim-osman-is-upset-because-dc-sp-did-not-come-to-the-rally/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 20:41:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10889</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Narayanganj Deputy Commissioner and Superintendent of Police did not come even after being invited to the rally organized against &#8216;Drugs, Terrorism, Chadambaji, Evetizing, Land Robbery&#8217; in Narayanganj. Member of Parliament of Narayanganj-4 Constituency Shamim Osman is involved in this. Shamim Osman said, &#8216;I am embarrassed by the question raised due to the absence of administration ... <a title="Shamim Osman is upset because DC-SP did not come to the rally" class="read-more" href="/shamim-osman-is-upset-because-dc-sp-did-not-come-to-the-rally/" aria-label="More on Shamim Osman is upset because DC-SP did not come to the rally">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Narayanganj Deputy Commissioner and Superintendent of Police did not come even after being invited to the rally organized against &#8216;Drugs, Terrorism, Chadambaji, Evetizing, Land Robbery&#8217; in Narayanganj. Member of Parliament of Narayanganj-4 Constituency Shamim Osman is involved in this. </p>
<p>Shamim Osman said, &#8216;I am embarrassed by the question raised due to the absence of administration officials in the rally called against drugs, terrorism, extortion. I will seek an answer to the question why the officials of the district and police administration did not come in the presence of the prime minister in the next national parliament session. I will seek an explanation as to why the servants of the republic did not come after calling a member of parliament from the government.&#8217; </p>
<p>At that time, the member of parliament of Narayanganj-4 constituencies warned the administration officials and said that if the people come out on the streets, they don&#8217;t want the administration. But then no one can stay.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/shamim-osman-is-upset-because-dc-sp-did-not-come-to-the-rally/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sharjah bound plane returned to Chittagong with 149 passengers after 2 hours of take off</title>
		<link>/sharjah-bound-plane-returned-to-chittagong-with-149-passengers-after-2-hours-of-take-off/</link>
					<comments>/sharjah-bound-plane-returned-to-chittagong-with-149-passengers-after-2-hours-of-take-off/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 20:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10887</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A Sharjah-bound Air Arabia flight turned back 2 hours after leaving Chittagong Shah Amanat Airport due to a mechanical fault. The plane landed safely at the airport at 9:35 pm on Saturday. Earlier, the Sharjah-bound flight left Chittagong Airport with 149 passengers on Saturday around 7:30 pm. After the flight approached Kolkata, the aircraft experienced ... <a title="Sharjah bound plane returned to Chittagong with 149 passengers after 2 hours of take off" class="read-more" href="/sharjah-bound-plane-returned-to-chittagong-with-149-passengers-after-2-hours-of-take-off/" aria-label="More on Sharjah bound plane returned to Chittagong with 149 passengers after 2 hours of take off">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Sharjah-bound Air Arabia flight turned back 2 hours after leaving Chittagong Shah Amanat Airport due to a mechanical fault. The plane landed safely at the airport at 9:35 pm on Saturday.</p>
<p>Earlier, the Sharjah-bound flight left Chittagong Airport with 149 passengers on Saturday around 7:30 pm. After the flight approached Kolkata, the aircraft experienced an electrical problem. </p>
<p>Chittagong Shah Amanat International Airport Director Group Captain Taslim Ahmed confirmed this information.</p>
<p>Group Captain Taslim said, after the mechanical problem, the pilot brought the plane back quickly without taking any risk. It is now at the airport. It was removed from the airport after landing. Mechanical troubleshooting is in progress. Passengers are accommodated in airport lounges and served meals. Overnight accommodation is being arranged for the passengers of the flight.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/sharjah-bound-plane-returned-to-chittagong-with-149-passengers-after-2-hours-of-take-off/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 64/89 objects using Redis
Page Caching using Redis 
Database Caching using Redis

Served from: _ @ 2024-01-27 20:46:41 by W3 Total Cache
-->